# ZAHRA ABDULKAREM

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

# **CONTACT**

+966 595415591

☑ zahra9amdulkarem@gmail.com

Makkah, Saudi Arabia

zahra-abdulkarem.github.io/ resume/

in linkedin.com/in/zahraabdoulkarem

## **EDUCATION**

 THE-EIGHTH HIGH SCHOOL

Natural Sciences · (January 2018 - August 2020)

### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- · CSS / SASS
- Javascript
- · React.js
- Bootstrap5
- MongoDB
- Express
- Next.js

### **LANGUAGES**

English (Professional Working)

Arabic (Native or Bilingual)

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a front end web developer I fully rely on my works to present myself because I fully trust their quality, and you can view them from here https://github.com/zahra abdulkarem I started learning this field in 2022 and I have done some personal projects, and I am still learning and developing skills and experience in the field of front-end development, back-end development and problem-solving.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

VEGGO

Frontend Developer June 2023

- Present (2 months)

I started working as a front-end developer with VegGo, the first organization in the Middle East and North Africa that cares about animal rights, health and plant health.

#### PRIVATE TEACHER

Mathematics Teacher March 2021 - Present (2 years 5 months)

I taught mathematics and computer science privately to primary and middle school students, and I trained them to solve complex mathematical issues, logical thinking, and detailed problemsolving.

#### SELF-EMPLOYED

Frontend Web Developer July 2022 - July 2023 (1 year 1 month)

Building, designing and developing website interfaces